<?xml version="1.0" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel>
<title>Computer Language Shootout</title><description>Compare programming language performance on a few dozen flawed benchmarks and contribute faster more-elegant programs.</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/</link>
<item><title>20th Nov, Debian computer language benchmarks measured</title><description>AWK gawk, AWK mawk, Ada 95 GNAT, Bash, C Intel, C Tiny, C gcc, C# Mono, C++ Intel, C++ g++, Clean, Curry, D Digital Mars, Dylan Gwydion, Eiffel SmartEiffel, Emacs Lisp Xemacs, Erlang, Erlang HiPE, Felix, Forth GForth, Fortran Intel, Groovy, Haskell GHC, Haskell HUGS, Icon, Io, Java GCJ, Java GIJ, Java JDK -server, Java Kaffe, Java SableVM, JavaScript SpiderMonkey, Lisp CMUCL, Lisp GNU, Lisp Newlisp, Lisp Poplisp, Lisp SBCL, Lisp librep, Lua, Mercury, Mozart/Oz, Nice, OCaml, OCaml (bytecode), Oberon-2 OO2C, Oberon-2 XDS, Objective C GNU, PHP , Pascal Free Pascal, Perl, Pike, Prolog Ciao, Prolog GNU, Prolog SWI, Python, Python Psyco, Rexx Regina, Ruby, S-Lang, SML MLton, SML Poly/ML, SML SML/NJ, Scheme Bigloo, Scheme Chicken, Scheme Guile, Scheme MZC, Scheme MzScheme, Scheme Stalin, Smalltalk GST, Tcl, elastiC :: ackermann, array (deprecate), binary-trees, chameneos (new), cheap-concurrency, concatenate (deprecate), count-words (deprecate), deque (deprecate), dispatch (deprecate), echo (deprecate), exception (deprecate), fannkuch, fasta, fibonacci (deprecate), harmonic, hashtable (deprecate), health (alpha), heapsort (deprecate), implicit ode (deprecate), k-nucleotide, mandelbrot, matrix (deprecate), n-body, nested-loop, nsieve, nsieve-bits, object (deprecate), object-methods (deprecate), pidigits, primes (deprecate), random, ray-tracer (deprecate), regex (deprecate), regex-dna (new), reverse-complement, spectral-norm, spellcheck (deprecate), startup, statistics (deprecate), sum-file, takfp, tcp-echo (deprecate), tcp-request-reply, tcp-socket (alpha), tcp-stream (deprecate), threads-prodcon (deprecate), word-frequency (deprecate)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/</link></item>
<item><title>19th Nov, Debian computer language benchmarks measured</title><description>Eiffel SmartEiffel :: pidigits</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/</link></item>
<item><title>19th Nov, Debian computer language benchmarks measured</title><description>AWK gawk, AWK mawk, Ada 95 GNAT, Bash, C Intel, C Tiny, C gcc, C# Mono, C++ Intel, C++ g++, Clean, Curry, D Digital Mars, Dylan Gwydion, Eiffel SmartEiffel, Emacs Lisp Xemacs, Erlang, Erlang HiPE, Felix, Forth GForth, Fortran Intel, Groovy, Haskell GHC, Haskell HUGS, Icon, Io, Java GCJ, Java GIJ, Java JDK -server, Java Kaffe, Java SableVM, JavaScript SpiderMonkey, Lisp CMUCL, Lisp GNU, Lisp Newlisp, Lisp Poplisp, Lisp SBCL, Lisp librep, Lua, Mercury, Mozart/Oz, Nice, OCaml, OCaml (bytecode), Oberon-2 OO2C, Oberon-2 XDS, Objective C GNU, PHP , Pascal Free Pascal, Perl, Pike, Prolog Ciao, Prolog GNU, Prolog SWI, Python, Python Psyco, Rexx Regina, Ruby, S-Lang, SML MLton, SML Poly/ML, SML SML/NJ, Scheme Bigloo, Scheme Chicken, Scheme Guile, Scheme MZC, Scheme MzScheme, Scheme Stalin, Smalltalk GST, Tcl, elastiC :: ackermann, array (deprecate), binary-trees, chameneos (new), cheap-concurrency, concatenate (deprecate), count-words (deprecate), deque (deprecate), dispatch (deprecate), echo (deprecate), exception (deprecate), fannkuch, fasta, fibonacci (deprecate), harmonic, hashtable (deprecate), health (alpha), heapsort (deprecate), implicit ode (deprecate), k-nucleotide, mandelbrot, matrix (deprecate), n-body, nested-loop, nsieve, nsieve-bits, object (deprecate), object-methods (deprecate), pidigits, primes (deprecate), random, ray-tracer (deprecate), regex (deprecate), regex-dna (new), reverse-complement, spectral-norm, spellcheck (deprecate), startup, statistics (deprecate), sum-file, takfp, tcp-echo (deprecate), tcp-request-reply, tcp-socket (alpha), tcp-stream (deprecate), threads-prodcon (deprecate), word-frequency (deprecate)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/</link></item>
<item><title>19th Nov, Gentoo computer language benchmarks measured</title><description>D Digital Mars, Eiffel SmartEiffel, Groovy, Haskell GHC, Io, JavaScript SpiderMonkey, Lisp CMUCL, Lisp SBCL, Lua, Perl, Pike, Prolog SWI, Python, Python Psyco, Rexx Regina, Ruby, Tcl :: ackermann, binary-trees, chameneos (new), cheap-concurrency, fannkuch, fasta, harmonic, k-nucleotide, mandelbrot, n-body, nsieve, nsieve-bits, pidigits, random, regex-dna (new), reverse-complement, spectral-norm, startup, sum-file, takfp, tcp-request-reply</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/</link></item>
<item><title>18th Nov, Gentoo computer language benchmarks measured</title><description>Clean, D Digital Mars, Groovy, Io, JavaScript SpiderMonkey, Lua, Nice, Perl, Pike, Prolog SWI, Python, Python Psyco, Rebol, Rexx Regina, Ruby, Tcl :: ackermann, binary-trees, chameneos (new), cheap-concurrency, fannkuch, fasta, harmonic, k-nucleotide, mandelbrot, nsieve, pidigits, random, reverse-complement, spectral-norm, startup, sum-file, takfp, tcp-request-reply</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/</link></item>
<item><title>Scala programming language installed</title><description>Scala is now installed - please contribute faster more-elegant Scala programs for the benchmark problems. (See the "How can I help?" FAQ.)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/scala.php</link></item>
<item><title>SWI Prolog programming language installed</title><description>SWI Prolog is now installed - please contribute faster more-elegant SWI Prolog programs for the benchmark problems. (See the "How can I help?" FAQ.)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/prolog.php</link></item>
<item><title>REBOL programming language installed</title><description>REBOL is now installed - please contribute faster more-elegant REBOL programs for the benchmark problems. (See the "How can I help?" FAQ.)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/rebol.php</link></item>
<item><title>Groovy programming language installed</title><description>Groovy is now installed - please contribute faster more-elegant Groovy programs for the benchmark problems. (See the "How can I help?" FAQ.)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/groovy.php</link></item>
<item><title>Io programming language installed</title><description>Io is now installed - please contribute faster more-elegant Io programs for the benchmark problems. (See the "How can I help?" FAQ.)</description><link>http://shootout.alioth.debian.org/gp4/io.php</link></item>
</channel></rss>
